Contact

mfernamb@med.umich.edu

www.linkedin.com/in/michelle-fernamberg-mha-bsn-rn-cnml-21924463 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Nursing
Patient Safety
Inpatient

Michelle Fernamberg MHA BSN RN CNML

Senior Nurse Director and Administrative Director University of Michigan Medical Group

Ann Arbor

Summary

Experienced Director of Nursing with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Patient Safety, Acute Care, Inpatient Rehabilitation, Ambulatory Care, Electronic Medical Record (EMR), and Nursing. Strong healthcare services professional with a Master's Degree focused in Health/Health Care Administration/Management from Eastern Michigan University.

Experience

Michigan Medicine
11 years 1 month

Administrative Director August 2020 - Present (1 month)

Senior Nurse Director January 2018 - Present (2 years 8 months) Ann Arbor

Clinical Nursing Director March 2017 - January 2018 (11 months) Ann Arbor

Nurse Manager August 2009 - March 2017 (7 years 8 months)

Allegiance Health
10 years 8 months

Nurse Manager May 1999 - August 2009 (10 years 4 months)

Nurse Educator

January 1999 - May 1999 (5 months)

IVOnyx Home Infusion Home Infusion Coordinator 1997 - 1999 (2 years) Livonia

Sinai Hospital Staff Registered Nurse 1995 - 1997 (2 years)

Education

Baylor University

Doctorate of Nursing Practice, Executive Nurse Leader · (2020 - 2021)

Eastern Michigan University

Master's Degree, Health/Health Care Administration/

Management · (2005 - 2007)

Eastern Michigan University

Bachelor's degree, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (1996 - 1999)

Jackson College

Associate of Science - AS, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse \cdot (1993 - 1995)